now you won’t burn
сейчас ты уж не будешь подгорать
And podgor let’s not burn I
А подгор давай не будешь подгорать буду
will burn I’ll immediately say I’ll burn Well,
буду подгорать Сразу говорю буду
your last name accordingly yes yes accordingly there is
подгорать Ну фамилия тебя соответственно
something there is something serious to say there is yes let’s give
что-то серьёзное сказать есть есть давай
something on history So Gumilyov
давай что-нибудь по истории Так гумилёв
is not a historian  Let's talk about
это не историк Давай поговорим
something about the history not on the left, let's
что-нибудь за историю не по лёву давай
not give on the left, I was interested in reading Yes,
не давай по лёву мне интересно читал
you can formulate it briefly And
Да можешь сформулировать кратко А как
you know what his mother's name was, I don't know at all what
его маму звали знаешь вообще не знаю как
his mother's name was Anna Akhmatova super
его маму звали Анна Ахматова супер
Akhmetova Akhmatova Akhmetova Akhmatova
Ахметова Ахматова Ахметова Ахматова ещё
Yanukovych also said Onana Akhmetova everyone
Янукович говорил онана Ахметова все
knows Ukraine  neta Akhmetova, look at
знают Укра нета Ахметова вот смотрите в
what Gumilyov’s concept is
чём вот концепция Гумилёва
civilizational,
цивилизационная
he Yes, by the way, so new Well, this is what’s
он Да кстати так новенькой Ну так в это
his name Well,
как его
you know Yes, I know And you can M what
Ну ты знаешь Да я знаю А вы можете М что
are passionaries according to
такое пассионарии по
Gumilyov We will discuss something or
гумилёв Мы что-то будем обсуждать или
some concept in the book  Well,
какую-то концепцию а книж дук Ну ну что
well, what are passionaries according to the
таки Что такое пассионарии по
left I don’t like those, I
лёву я вот те вот
can
могу
imagine Ukraine. Here in this
Украины представляешь Вот в этой в этой
book what is written about passionaries Yes,
книжке что написано про пассионарии Да
a lot of things Well, who are the passionaries
много что Ну что Кто такие пассионарии
according to Gumilyov I don’t like Yes, I didn’t unwind it
по гумилёв ше не
orche don’t
люблю Да не по размотал орче не Не
put it off Don’t put it off the book  Don’t
откладывай Не откладывай книжку Не
put the book down, it’s lying nearby. Don’t
откладывай книжку она рядом лежит не Не
put the book down. Yes, it’s
откладывай книжку Да
nearby. What is the essence of Gumilyov’s idea about
рядом в ч В чём суть идеи Гумилёва про
this, so to speak, Eurasian
вот эту так так сказать евразийскую
Civilization,
Цивилизацию
that there
что ну что ты
wasn’t even a picture?  - a thick book with
было взять какую-то толстую книжку с
some maps, yes.
какими-то картами да А
Can you tell me at least one idea from this
можешь Скажи хоть вот одну идею из этой
book? I have a thick book lying behind me, you
книги у меня сзади толстая книжка лежит
see, behind me I don’t care, it’s fat, you tell me
видишь у меня сза пофиг толста ты скажи
according to Gumilyov, you’re really running away,
по по Гумилёва ты убегаешь реально
you see at least one idea from behind me, fat
видишь у меня сзади толстая одну хотя бы
Gumilyov's books Tell
идею из книги Гумилёва Скажи
me, you don't even know his father's name
мне ты его даже отца не знаешь как звать
Don't care What kind of father are you based on Gumilyov's book
Да пофиг Как отца ты по книге Гумилёва
What idea
Какая идея у него
did he have For which of the books is
была По какой из книг
this one that you are holding now and
вот вот это которое ты держишь сейчас а
which one I was holding Come on, say at least
какую я держал Давай давай говори хоть
one Tell me one thesis not  one thesis
одну Скажи мне один тезис не один тезис
from this book
из этой книги
tell me who the passionaries are you don’t know
скажи кто такие пассионарии ты не знаешь
what the essence of civilizations there is gender you don’t
в чём суть там цивилизации пол ты не
know at least one take it Open
знаешь хоть одну возьми Открой вот
here the contents and according to the content tell me how it is here just history here just
здесь просто история здесь просто
history LW was not a historian
история ЛВ не историк
take it Open and read there is a preface there
возьми Открой и прочитай там предисловие
here from the publisher Who is
есть вот от издателя Кто такой
Gumilyov, read Who is Gumilyov
гумилёв вот прочитай Кто такой гумилёв
right there in the book and you will open it
вот там в книжке прямо открываешь и ты
directly Who is Gumilyov,
прочитаешь Кто такой гумилёв прямо
I can open it in the back here and
откроешь вот я сзади могу вот да
read who Gumilyov is,
прочитай кто такой гумилёв
come on Lev Gumilyov
давай Лев гумилёв
[music]
[музыка]
92 an outstanding historian and ethnographer and
92 выдающийся историк и этнограф и
Vesto Kovet  Doctor of Historical and
весто ковет доктор исторических и
Geographical Sciences, son of the famous
географических наук сын знаменитых
parents Anna Akhmatova and Nikolai
родителей Анны Ахматовой и Николая
Mev
мева
Akhmetova, Yanukovych also spoke to Yana
ахметовой Янукович ещ говорил Яна
Akhmetova, he
ахметовой он
developed the famous
разработал разра знаменитую
theory of passionarity Yes, which
теорию пассионарности
explains the patterns of the
Да объясняющую закономерности
historical process Well blah blah blah well
исторического процесса Ну бла-бла-бла ну
yes blah blah yes So here I am, I am you
вот да бла-бла да Так вот я же я же вас
that's why I asked yes What is the point Who are the
поэтому и спросил да В чём суть Кто
passionaries according to
такие пассионарии по
Gumilyov or have you not yet read this
гумилёв или вы пока ещё не читали эту
book just waved cards Yes not all not
книгу только махали картами Да не всю не
all not all Well, not like not all Until where did
всю не всю Ну так не как не всю До куда
you read tell me To which page I will
вы дочитали скажите До какой страницы я
tell you And they were there  According to the script,
вам скажу И были там по сценарии уже или
have you already read this book or haven’t? Say
не были ты вот именно эту книжку читал
yes Tell me Which page have you
Скажите да Скажите До какой страницы вы
read? I’ll be honest, I bought it today,
дочитали буду честен я её и сегодня
I only bought the pictures. Everything, let’s
я только картинки
still win for now,
стали Всё давай повна перемога пока
Glory to Ukraine,
Слава Украине
let’s have complete intellectual
Давай полное интеллектуальное
superiority like Ukraine over Russia, it’s
превосходство типа Украины над Россией
just a thrill to win, butt  Damn,
просто кайф перемога попка блин це
I just got high, yeah So cool, yes, I
Просто я кайфанул да Так круто да я
got mev's book, look,
достал книжечку мева смотри
Dude, I read such books And you just
Чувак я читал такие книги А ты только
waved Her, in short, it's just, I got high, damn, just
короче это просто я кайфанул блин просто
damn, for the sake of tre subscribe to the channel Yes Like
ну блин за це тре пишиться на канал Да
there, I don't know the rooms, leave a comment
Поставьте лайк там не знаю залы комент
Donat in short  on Andron’s father
закиньте Донат короче на отца Андрона
just simply for the intelligence of his father Anro I’ll
просто просто вот за интеллект отца анро
throw him a donat I just don’t
треба ему закину Донат просто треба я не
know so and so impudent Popik ass Popik
знаю такой-то дерзкий Попик жопик Попик
ass In short, as it is So he sat in
жопик Короче как типа есть Так сел в
a puddle, in short, he drove him into the ass,
лужу короче пок загнал его в задницу
in short, throw a Donat for a cool dressing down of
короче закиньте Донат за классный разнос
his ass Yes  damn you're waving
поенари попку Да бляха ты машешь
Gumilyov damn it and you don't know what
Гумилёва блин и не знаешь что такое
posna is even Damn if you read it in the back
посна даже Блин если ты читал то сзади
when you damn bought this book You should have
когда ты эту книжку блин покупал Ты бы
already heard such a word It's just
уже хоть Слышал такое слово Это просто
cruel
жесть
like this is all Russia Yes all Russia is like that
как вот это вся Россия Да вся Россия
Yes the main thing is to shake the books Open
такая Да главное потрясти книжки Открыть
some  then a map and say here there
какую-то карту и сказать вот тут Украины
was no Ukraine, the dude actually drew his own maps
не было чувак вообще рисовал свои карты
whichever he wanted,
какие хотел
like Class Class I
типа Класс Класс Я
got high I keep thinking wine like I read yes I
кайфанул Я всё думаю вин типа Читал да я
thought now we’ll talk about now we’ll
думал сейчас мы о сейчас поговорим
talk like generally cool
поговорим типа вообще класс
[laughter]
[смех]
And the roasting is cool I got high just
А классна прожарка я кайфанул просто
really got high  It was cool to write
кайфанул реально це было круто пидпишить
to my Telegram directly at the same time axis VN and so much more
на мий Telegram прямо зараз ось ВН а
and more respectfully YouTube took
пок це дуже и дуже важливо YouTube заня
us through srg org to your ban and even
нас через срг ор в твый бан и дуже
more video I don’t show people immediately I don’t
багато вдео не показую людям вчасно не
show information about streams for this
показуе информация про стримы тому для
purpose for Mali operational link
того щоб ми Мали оперативный звязок
to write directly  zazar and while there in telegra
пишиться прямо зараз а пок там в телегра
okm video tezh va and korisna information and
окм видео теж ва и корисна информация и
pon z you trimati postiyny operational
пон з вами тримати постийний оперативный
link
звязок
nezalezhno in togo chi show you the process
незалежно в того чи покаже вам проце
YouTube Slava ukraini
YouTube Слава украини
write
пиши